I'm saying no one can fix her not even us no way we we've gone everywhere without any problems
until now in theory even if we did everything we could the probability of your ship lasting
till the next island is zero
Mary tell me it's what he said true you'll never sail again
pirate abduction incident and a pirate ship that can only await her end
this sucks I'm sorry Sonji I was so focused on the books that I didn't notice when she left
there's nothing you should have to apologize for I just assumed that the person I saw walking with
Robin had to have been you and your human form which begs the question who was that masked man
and how were they able to disappear so suddenly yeah even Robin's scent disappeared
I hope everything's all right I feel uneasy do you need an examination no that's not what I meant
it's what Aokiji said his words keep repeating what did he say that worries you it was all that
terrible stuff he said about Robin's past and then very soon we'd regret her being on our crew
oh yeah right so do you think what he said might have had something to do with her disappearance
I don't know but I know we're getting nowhere looking for her let's head back to the ship for now
if nothing's wrong she'll come back on her own eventually yeah you're right hurry back to the Mary
what
What?! You can't fix the going, Mary?! Why not?!
I thought all of you were supposed to be awesome shipwrights!
Don't worry about the money! Look, we got plenty!
It's not about the money, son.
No matter how much you pay, that ship can't be restored to how she used to be.
To be honest, I'm rather impressed you were able to get that old girl this far,
considering the condition that she's currently in.
What's that supposed to mean?! What exactly is going on with the Mary?!
Do you know what the keel is, immoral girl?
Immo- The thing at the bottom of the boat?
Yeah. It's the most important piece of lumber on a ship.
It crosses from stem to stern and provides support.
When you build a ship, you start off by placing the keel.
Then you set the wood for the stem, the stern, the frame, frame brackets and deck beams.
All of the pieces are carefully assembled together, with the keel serving as the core.
It's the very backbone, framework and life of every vessel constructed.
And when it's severely damaged, then that's the end of her.
You can't just replace it with a new one.
That'd be the same thing as building a new ship from scratch.
That's the reason we, or anyone, won't be able to fix her.
Your ship's just a bunch of wood stuck together, awaiting her end.
Hey you! Don't say such horrible things!
Horrible or not, it's the truth.
Okay, fine then. Just rebuild her from the ground up, like you said before. Build another Going Mary.
Cuckoo! Sorry, not possible.
Why not?
We could build you a very similar ship, but no one can build you one that would be exactly the same.
Nowhere in the world are there two completely identical ships. It simply can't be done.
What do you mean? Why?
Tell me, are there any trees in the world that grow exactly the same way?
A sailing ship is mostly built out of lumber, so the overall size and shape of a vessel is determined by the type of wood used.
That's why an exact duplicate of your ship can't be built by us or anyone, even when using the same blueprints.
If we made a ship like that with those specifications, the ones who would notice the difference,
and feel that it's a completely different ship, would be all of you guys! Cuckoo!
No way! So you're saying it's absolutely impossible for us to continue sailing on the Going Mary?
Unfortunately, yes. You can either wait around for her to sink, or you can dismantle her immediately.
A real Carabelle!
What a cool ship! Have you guys seen the front? It's totally awesome!
Okay! It's all done! Now the Going Mary has everything she could possibly need!
Well, your ship is on her last legs. Why don't you look at this as an opportunity?
You happen to be in the best place in the world to buy a new ship. You have money, right?
I understand that your ship was a Carabelle. Sailing on the Grand Line in an old ship like that would be difficult to begin with.
No way! We're not getting a new ship!
Luffy...
The Mary is...
The Going Mary is the ship of the Straw Hat Pirates! If she's repaired, then she can still sail!
She'll be fine! You'll see! She got us here today, didn't she?
And you tell us out of nowhere she can't sail anymore? I can't believe that! I won't!
You guys are saying that because you don't know her! You have no idea how strong she is!
Then your plan is to keep sailing her until she sinks? I'm shocked!
So, this is the decision of the ship's captain?
This discussion is over for now. Just think about it. If you decide to buy a ship, let me know. My people can help.
If you're able to spend $300 million, we can build a state-of-the-art ship for you. Califa?
Here. If you'd look this over, please. It's a catalog of our new and our used models. Use it as a price reference.
Hey, Iceberg! There's someone at the front gate who wants to see you. Hmm?
There doesn't seem to be anyone on your appointment schedule for today.
It looks like those world government officials again. Should I tell them you're unavailable?
Well...
Yes, please. Say I'm gone. By the way, Lulu, you've got quite a case of bedhead.
Oops! How embarrassing. My apologies. Anyway, I'll ask them to leave.
Uh, thanks. I appreciate it.
Hold it right there, Iceberg. Hmm?
Looks like you're here after all.
Hey, you two need to hide. Government officials are here.
What? Uh, okay.
Well, hello again, Corgi. As you can see, I'm not here today.
Yes, you are. Come now. I've come all the way out here by sea train. Don't turn me away. It's impolite.
For some reason, I detect the scent of pirates.
Whatever. In any case, I want to talk to you.
I don't like you. Go away.
Are you a child?
Uh-uh. I'm totally an adult.
Then start acting like one.
There's something of special importance I need to discuss with you.
I would appreciate it if you'd hear me out.
Come. Let's talk this over in private.
Those government guys are so damn persistent.
What the hell do they want with Iceberg anyway?
Look, it has nothing to do with us. Probably political stuff.
Should I beat them up?
I wouldn't. I mean, they're government guys after all.
What? What's wrong?
Something seemed weird about these bags when I grabbed them.
They're really light.
Huh? What do you mean?
What do you mean?
Oh, come on. Stop kidding around.
How could they be with all of that money inside?
Hey, who's that?
What's with the screaming?
Idiots! What the hell are you...
Hot lady!
If you sit like that, everyone can see your...
Don't tell me.
There's no way.
I don't want to look.
200 million!
Gone! It's really gone!
Wait, look at these bags! They're not even ours!
What are we going to do?
Hey, hey! Keep it down!
What's wrong?
Our money. Our money's gone.
Finished. Got disappeared.
What?
Holly, was it you again?
Huh? No!
Honest?
Why would I lie?
You mean it?
Yes, I mean it.
They're so noisy.
Hey, Kaku, question for you.
Why were you hanging out with the Frankie family earlier?
What are you talking about?
I haven't been anywhere near a single member of the Frankie family all day.
That's strange.
Huh.
I was so certain that I saw your long nose.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hold on a sec!
That's Usa!
You saw him with the Frankie family?
Well, you could say he was with them.
Or maybe you could say he was being dragged away.
That's called kidnapping!
Loopy, we gotta find him!
Hey, hold on!
Where are you going to look?
Wait for me, Usaq!
Wait for me, Money!
I'm coming!
Hey, where can I find the Frankie family's hideout?
It's not really a hideout.
It's more like a workshop.
From where your ship is docked, it's way up the seashore to the northeast.
It's off by itself.
You can't miss it.
It's called the Frankie House.
Loopy!
What was he thinking?
There's no way he could find Usaq in this place all by himself.
I can't keep looking for him right now.
Before I do anything else, I need to take this money back to the ship.
If I march in there demanding our 200 million back while holding 100 million,
I'd be asking them to steal that money, too.
Yagra, please take me to the bull shop.
Shortest route possible.
I'll take Zoro and the others with me and teach them a lesson.
Stealing from pirates?
Frankie family, that makes you the lowest of the low!
First floor, Backstreet Shopping District.
Please proceed with caution.
Thank you and have a wonderful day!
Hurry, I'm counting on you!
What's her problem?
Hey!
Watch where you're going!
I'm sorry, sir!
I hope Usaq was able to escape from them, somehow.
This is terrible!
Where's this guy from?
Hey!
Does anybody know him?
Who is he?
What's with them?
Yagra, wait!
Hold on a second!
Stop!
Usaq!
Hey!
Say something!
Are you alright?
Open your eyes!
Usaq!
Hey!
Wake up!
Excuse me, but are you two pirates by any chance?
Shut up!
Stop scaring and mind your own business!
Oh no!
Usaq!
I did this to you!
Was it the Frankie family?
It was!
It happened because I'm weak!
They took...
They took all the money!
Nabi!
How can I face the others now?
We were finally able to fix the fairy!
I'm so ashamed!
Damn it!
Usaq, I understand.
Don't worry about the money.
We'll get it back together.
He's been beaten pretty badly.
I probably shouldn't move him.
Look, stay right here, okay?
I'm gonna go back to the ship to get the others to come and help.
Chopper will have you fixed up good as new in no time.
And listen, don't worry about the stolen money, alright?
From what I've heard, their hideout isn't too far away from here.
We'll crush them and that'll be the end of it, okay?
Hey!
You think this is some kind of show?
Get lost!
Stay put, okay?
I'm going to get you some help.
I'll be right back!
Let's go!
Okay, let's go!
Hurry, Yakurak, go faster!
Whee!
Ah!
Our runaway ball!
We were ugly able to fix the fairy!
No matter how much you pay, that ship can't be restored to how she used to be.
Whether we decide to give in and buy a new ship,
or we have someone else manage to fix and improve the Mary,
if we don't put the entire $300 million into this,
our future journeys together will be difficult for sure.
We need that money. All of it. We have to get it back.
What? Is that true?
Well, that's what the shipwright said.
The ship.
It can't be fixed, even if we have money?
Then, then what's going to happen to the Mary?
Beats me.
Honestly, it really just depends on how Luffy and the others react after hearing the assessment.
Either way, I'm sure they'll get it sorted out while they're at the shipyard.
It just seems so extreme. I mean, look at her.
Same old Mary that she's always been.
We've traveled together on this ship all the way from the East Blue to this place. Why now?
You just answered your own question.
Human beings become stronger, hardship after hardship.
But ships are different. Their wounds just pile up.
It's so hard to accept. And what is Usopp going to say when he hears about all of this?
I don't want to leave her. I love the Mary.
I know we all do. But her wounds are too deep. There's nothing we can do.
The Mary's in trouble and Robin's still missing.
I'm worried about both of them.
Hey, everyone!
Look! It's Nami and she's alone!
Hmm? That's weird. I wonder what happened to Luffy and Usopp.
Hi, Nami! Is everything all right?
What do you think, bro? Awesome, right?
Incredible. You guys are amazing.
Now that we have this much money, we'll be able to get what we've always wanted.
We actually did it, didn't we?
After three years, our perseverance has finally paid off.
I'm stoked!
Me too.
Every time we'd have a little money, we'd bet it all on the Yogg-O'-Races!
And lose every time!
Each time we'd collect a criminal's bounty, we'd party and drink!
And spend it all!
We could never ever save up the 200 million berries that we needed.
Until now!
We finally have enough to get it done!
And then some!
You guys did a hell of a job!
Now then, I know it isn't much, but here's five million berries to show you how grateful I am.
Eat, drink, and have a blast!
That's our bro!
Party time!
What the hell?
What was that?
Show yourself!
What fool would dare to oppose the Frankie family?
Huh?
It's that weakling we ran into earlier!
How did you even manage to stand up?
Give us our money back?
Give us our money back, you say?
Hmm.
Does that mean you're one of the Straw Hats?
That's right, bro, he totally is!
I was expecting all of the Straw Hats crew to be really strong, but this one's not at all!
Yeah, he's a complete weakling, what a joke!
Mind your own damn business!
What's he doing?
You've got some guts trying to take back the money all by yourself.
But I'm afraid I can't let you have it.
Give it back!
We need the money to fix the berry!
Her scars are deep!
That's our money!
It's to heal her wounds, understand me?
You can't have it!
Give it back to me right now!
That's all!
On the next Wood Feast, rescuing our friend, raid on the Frankie House!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!